{"data":{"questions":[{"correct_answer":"Tell your parents and contact the site administrator.","option_1":"Show it to your friends","option_2":"Ignore it","option_3":"Show it to your friends","option_4":"Tell your parents and contact the site administrator.","question":"If someone creates a social-networking page in your name you should"},{"correct_answer":"Both A and B","option_1":"Leave the site","option_2":"Tell an adult","option_3":"Click on another part, maybe it will be better","option_4":"Both a and b","question":"If a website makes you feel uncomfortable you should"},{"correct_answer":"Flaming (sending hurtful or mean messages)","option_1":"Flaming (sending hurtful or mean messages)","option_2":"Trick or treat","option_3":"Email","option_4":"All of the above","question":"Which of the following is a form of cyberbullying?"},{"correct_answer":"Tell or show it to a teacher or a parent","option_1":"Ignore it","option_2":"Tell or show it to a teacher or a parent","option_3":"Respond to the message","option_4":"Call 999","question":"If a message that is posted on-line is mean you should"},{"correct_answer":"Screen name","option_1":"Screen name","option_2":"School name and location","option_3":"Your real first name and last name","option_4":"Your phone number and address","question":"What information is okay to use on the internet?"},{"correct_answer":"Cyberbullying","option_1":"Cyberbullying","option_2":"Email","option_3":"Nice","option_4":"Feedback","question":"Harassment through the Internet that is rude and/or threatening is"},{"correct_answer":"Tell a teacher and change your password","option_1":"Ignore it","option_2":"Contact the police","option_3":"Tell a teacher and change your password","option_4":"Find out who gave out your password","question":"If someone steals your password at school you should"},{"correct_answer":"Save and show the messages to a parent, guardian or trusted adult","option_1":"Respond to the message and tell the person what you think","option_2":"Save and show the messages to a parent, guardian or trusted adult","option_3":"Just ignore the messages","option_4":"Delete and ignore the messages","question":"When you get a rude or hurtful message on the computer you should"},{"correct_answer":"All of the above","option_1":"Your email or other personal sites could be tampered with","option_2":"Someone could steal your identity online","option_3":"Your banking or shopping sites could be tampered with","option_4":"All of the above","question":"Giving your password to a friend could result in the following incidents:"},{"correct_answer":"Ask your parent/teacher permission to use the site.","option_1":"Click okay. Your parents/teachers won't mind.","option_2":"Ask your parent/teacher permission to use the site.","option_3":"Ask your friend for permission","option_4":"None of the above","question":"If a website asks for your parent's permission before you can use it, you should"},{"correct_answer":"Never","option_1":"Never","option_2":"If your online friend wants to meet you in a public place","option_3":"When your best friend has given out his/her information","option_4":"If you have been chatting with a friend online for several weeks and know that person well","question":"It is all right to give out personal information online in the following instances:"},{"correct_answer":"Something that is easy for you to remember, but hard for others to guess","option_1":"Something that is easy for you to remember, but hard for others to guess","option_2":"Your birthday","option_3":"Something only you and your best friend know","option_4":"Your pet's name","question":"Your passwords should be"},{"correct_answer":"","option_1":"Only your best friends","option_2":"Only the friends you trust","option_3":"Everyone","option_4":"Only your parents or guardians","question":"Who should you tell your passwords and usernames to?"},{"correct_answer":"Get parental permission","option_1":"Not worry about it because it's only online.","option_2":"Get parental permission","option_3":"Talk to a friend about what to do","option_4":"Both a and b","question":"Before putting personal information on a website I should"},{"correct_answer":"123456","option_1":"123456","option_2":"asdf","option_3":"Iloveyou","option_4":"monkey","question":"Ideally, what characters should you use in a password to make it strong?"},{"correct_answer":"All of the above","option_1":"Use mnemonics","option_2":"Develop a password strategy","option_3":"Use password management software with encryption.","option_4":"All of the above","question":"Strong passwords can be difficult to remember. What can you do to avoid forgetting them?"},{"correct_answer":"Choose something you can remember, but modify it with a complex pattern that only you know.","option_1":"Add a number or special character to the end of your old password.","option_2":"Pick something easy to remember, such as a football team or your birthday.","option_3":"Choose something quick and easy to type in so nobody can see it.","option_4":"Choose something you can remember, but modify it with a complex pattern.","question":"When it’s time to change your password, what’s the best way to choose a new one?"},{"correct_answer":"It depends!","option_1":"Less than an hour","option_2":"Less than a week","option_3":"Less than a month","option_4":"It depends!","question":"How long would it take an attacker to crack a 10 character password?"},{"correct_answer":"15 Characters","option_1":"8 Characters","option_2":"It doesn’t matter","option_3":"As long as possible","option_4":"15 Characters","question":"How long should a strong password be?"},{"correct_answer":"","option_1":"When someone steals your credit card","option_2":"When someone illegally takes posession of your personal data","option_3":"When someone dresses up like you","option_4":"When someone robs your house","question":"What is Identity Theft?"},{"correct_answer":"Do not provide personal information to the public","option_1":"Give out your information","option_2":"Keep your banking statements in reach of others","option_3":"Ask your neighbour to tell you your statements","option_4":"Do not provide personal information to the public","question":"How do you prevent Identity Theft?"},{"correct_answer":"RainbowFishMonkey900","option_1":"Your name","option_2":"Password","option_3":"RainbowFishMonkey900","option_4":"123","question":"Which of these is the most secure password?"},{"correct_answer":"Your ISP asking you by email to click on an unknown link.","option_1":"A popup on weight loss pills.","option_2":"An email getting people to sign a petition.","option_3":"Your ISP asking you by email to click on an unknown link.","option_4":"A popup showing how to bow to me correctly.","question":"Which one of these options present a red flag for a phishing scam?"},{"correct_answer":"Clown","option_1":"Clown","option_2":"Worm","option_3":"Botnet","option_4":"Trojan Horse","question":"Which one of these terms is not a type of malware? Maybe this can help?"},{"correct_answer":"Your bank account has been compromised. Give us your credit card number to get assistance from your bank.","option_1":"THIS IS SPAM","option_2":"New Youtube video uploaded","option_3":"LOL Lottery! The stakes are high, and you can win big!","option_4":"Your bank account has been compromised. Give us your credit card.","question":"Which one of these are potentially fraudulant spam?"},{"correct_answer":"Fishing","option_1":"Phishing","option_2":"Scam","option_3":"Spyware","option_4":"Fishing","question":"This technique tries to take information from the user"},{"correct_answer":"Personal Information","option_1":"Personal Information","option_2":"Being able to have another name.","option_3":"Send them emails.","option_4":"Take their victim's address for future use.","question":"Why is identity theft  something hackers usually go for?"},{"correct_answer":"","option_1":"Spam through forums","option_2":"Spam through messaging","option_3":"Spam through online gaming","option_4":"All the above","question":"How are there other ways spam can give tons and tons of junk?"},{"correct_answer":"ThEM(12)nkEy~Eats@BAnEnahs","option_1":"Monkey2","option_2":"M0nk3y1","option_3":"ThEM(12)nkEy~Eats@BAnEnahs","option_4":"Th3 m0nk3y 3475 b4n4n4s","question":"Now that you are an expert, choose the strongest password from this list:"}]}}
